|| LAB-NAME: Demo Lab
|| LAB-AUTHOR: Field Day

|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	a. Bunsen Burner
	Apply heat using the Bunsen Burner until T ≈ 320 K."
	Requirements: [(Temperature:320:5)]
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	a. Bunsen Burner
	Which property is held constant?"
	Answers: ["Pressure"(c), "Volume", "Temperature", "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multi-select-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	a. Bunsen Burner
	Which properties are changing?"
	Answers: ["Pressure", "Volume"(c), "Temperature"(c), "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	a. Cooling Coil
	Apply the cooling coil until T ≈ 300 K."
	Requirements: [(Temperature:300:5)]
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	b. Cooling Coil
	Which property is held constant?"
	Answers: ["Pressure"(c), "Volume", "Temperature", "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multi-select-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	b. Cooling Coil
	Which properties are changing?"
	Answers: ["Pressure", "Volume"(c), "Temperature"(c), "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	a. Weight
	Apply the weight until P ≈ 400 kPa."
	Requirements: [(Pressure:400:5)]
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	c. Weight
	Which property is held constant?"
	Answers: ["Pressure", "Volume", "Temperature", "None of the above"(c)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multi-select-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	c. Weight
	Which properties are changing?"
	Answers: ["Pressure"(c), "Volume"(c), "Temperature"(c), "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:



|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	a. Balloon
	Apply the balloon until P ≈ 50 kPa."
	Requirements: [(Pressure:50:5)]
|EfficiencyInfo:



|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	d. Balloon
	Which property is held constant?"
	Answers: ["Pressure", "Volume", "Temperature", "None of the above"(c)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multi-select-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"First, we’ll try out each feature of the simulator. Determine which property is being held constant and which one(s) are changing.
	d. Balloon
	Which properties are changing?"
	Answers: ["Pressure"(c), "Volume"(c), "Temperature"(c), "None of the above"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"	e. Volume Stops (clamp)
Apply a stop in the two-phase region, near V = 0.08 m³/kg."
	Requirements: [(VolumeStop:0.08:0.02)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"	e. Volume Stops (clamp)
Without moving your stop, apply heat until the simulation volume nears the volume of the stop."
	Requirements: [(Volume:0.08:0.02)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [word-bank]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"	e. Volume Stops (clamp)
As you continue to apply heat, which property is held constant?"
	Answers: ["Pressure", "Volume"(c), "Temperature", "Entropy", "Enthalpy", "Quality"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multi-select-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"	e. Volume Stops (clamp)
	Which properties are changing?"
	Answers: ["Pressure"(c), "Volume", "Temperature"(c)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "What region will the ball be in if T = 373.15 K and P < P_sat?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid", "Two-Phase"(c), "Superheated Vapor"]
|EfficiencyInfo:



|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "What region will the ball be in if T = 373.15 K and P > P_sat?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid"(c), "Two-Phase", "Superheated Vapor"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "What region will the ball be in if P = 101 kPa and T > 373.15 K?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid", "Two-Phase", "Superheated Vapor"(c)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "What region will the ball be in if P = 101 kPa and T < 373.15 K?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid"(c), "Two-Phase", "Superheated Vapor"]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"Grab the state ball and drop it into a starting position in the Superheated Vapor region with P ≈ 95 kPa."
	Requirements: [(Region:2:0), (Pressure:95:10)]
|EfficiencyInfo:




|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"Now apply the balloon and lower the pressure to 85 kPa (ambient pressure in Denver)."
	Requirements: [(Pressure:82.5:2.5)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question:
"Leave the balloon in place. Apply the insulation and cooling coil to bring the ball into the 2-phase region, maintaining P ≈ 85 kPa."
	Requirements: [(Pressure:82.5:3), (Region:1:0)]
|EfficiencyInfo:



|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "What is the saturation (boiling) temperature of water at 85 kPa?"
	Answers: ["≈ 348 K", "≈ 368 K"(c), "≈ 388 K", "≈ 408 K"]
|EfficiencyInfo:



|| END



